Finding aid for the Friends of the Los Angeles River records, 1987-2013 LSC.2215
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Activities, 1930-2013
  - Advocacy: Army Corps of Engineers and FoLAR, 1990-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control, Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA), 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control, Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control, Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control, Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control, Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA), 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control/Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA), 1993-1995 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control/Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA), 1995-1998 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control/Los Angeles County Drainage Area Project (LACDA), 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control, Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA), and El Nino, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Advocacy: Flood Control, Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA) Press, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - Advocacy: Los Angeles and San Gabriel Rivers Watershed Council, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advocacy: Los Angeles and San Gabriel Rivers Watershed Council, 2000s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advocacy: Los Angeles and San Gabriel Rivers Watershed Council, 2003-2006 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Advocacy: Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA)-DC Lobbying, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advocacy: Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA) Feasibility Study, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Advocacy: Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA) Negative Declaration, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advocacy: Los Angeles River Parkway, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Advocacy: Los Angeles River Watershed Task Force, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Advocacy: Plastic Bag Ban, 2005-2013 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Advocacy: Plastic Bag Ban, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Advocacy: Runoff, 1991-2012 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Advocacy: Water Management, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Advocacy: Water Recycling Projects, 1995-2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Advocacy: Water Quality Control Boards, 1989-1993 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Advocacy: Watershed Connectivity: Fish Study, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Advocacy: Willow Street Estuary Dredging, 1992-2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Audiovisual materials: "A Perspective on the Los Angeles River" videocassette (VHS), 8/30/1996 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: "A Treasure Beneath Our Feet" videocassette (VHS), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: ABC-Peter Jennings News, "Great Los Angeles River Clean Up" videocassette (VHS), 6/6/1992 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: ABC-Peter Jennings News, Los Angeles River piece videocassette (VHS), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: ABC News Peter Jennnigs Los Angeles River piece videocassette (VHS), October 1990 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: City Beat, Los Angeles County Drainage Area (LACDA) Project, City of Bellflower videocassette (VHS), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: City planning commission meeting sound disc (CD) (1 of 4), October 11, 2007 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: City planning commission meeting sound disc (CD) (2 of 4), October 11, 2007 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: City planning commission meeting sound disc (CD) (3 of 4), October 11, 2007 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: City planning commission meeting sound disc (CD) (4 of 4), October 11, 2007 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: Coors Pure Water 2000 news coverage, Friends of the Los Angeles River videocassette (VHS), May 1, 1993 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: FoLAR 1 and 2 videodisc (DVD), 3/08 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: FoLAR Clean Up Gateway Park videocassette (VHS), 1998 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Greenway Arts Alliance videocassette (VHS), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Howard Lindenmeyer, "Los Angeles River Clean Up" videocassette (VHS), April 1994 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Huell Howser, "Something Resembling a River" videocassette (VHS), July 17, 2002 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: "In Our Backyard" videocassette (VHS), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Intersection, "Los Angeles" videocassette (VHS), 10/29/1999 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: KCAL 9, "Los Angeles River" videocassette (Betacam), 24 July 1998 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: KCOP 11/16/1999 newscast, IF/LA River videocassette (VHS), 12/17/1999 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: La Vibora del Zacate (The Serpent of the Grass) videocassette (VHS), 2002 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Los Angeles River Clean Up videocassette (VHS), 1995 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Los Angeles River Clean Up videocassette (VHS), May 8-10, 1998 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Los Angeles River: The Infrastructural City videodisc (DVD), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Los Angeles River: Which Way LA sound disc (CD) (1 of 5), 7/15/1997 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: Los Angeles River: Which Way LA sound disc (CD) (2 of 5), 7/15/1997 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: Los Angeles River: Which Way LA sound disc (CD) (3 of 5), 7/15/1997 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: Los Angeles River: Which Way LA sound disc (CD) (4 of 5), 7/15/1997 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: Los Angeles Riverwatch videocassette (VHS), 2/3/2001 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Mighty Los Angeles River Roll On, The Dark Bob sound disc (CD), 1-16-1996 (Box 157)
  - Audiovisual materials: Public service announcements 35mm film reels (14 copies), 2008 (Box 151)
  - Audiovisual materials: "Rio: A manual for consciousness" videocassette (VHS), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Riofest v.1 videodiscs (2 DVDs), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Southbank Parkland Australia Riverfront Development videocassette (VHS), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Studio Charette videocassette (VHS), 1997 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Studio Charette videocassette (VHS), 1997 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: "Thank You" a low, low budget video by Jeff Vilencia videocassette (VHS), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: The Lower Arroyo-Restoration for the Future videocassette (VHS), 9/11/1998 (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: The River Under the City of Angels videodisc (DVD), undated (Box 156)
  - Audiovisual materials: Visiting with Huell Howser Episode #218, "Los Angeles River" videocassette (VHS) (2 copies), undated (Box 156)
  - Conferences: "America's Great Outdoors" White House Conference, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Conferences: Compton Gateway Symposium, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Conferences: Discovering the River at Central Library, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Conferences: Gathering at the River Oral History Event, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Conferences: Green Festival, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Conferences: Greening XI Conference, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Conferences: Re-Envisioning the Los Angeles River, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Conferences: Re-Thinking the River, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Conferences: River in the City Conference, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Conferences: River Through Downtown Conference, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 9-11)
  - Conferences: Science and Biology of Los Angeles River Conference, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Conferences: Southern California Environment and History Conference, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Conferences: Spanning History- Bridges of Los Angeles River Panel, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Conferences: Studio Stretch Planning Charette, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
  - Conferences: Taylor Yard Planning and Urban Design Workshop, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Conferences: Visions for the River Conference, 4 May 1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Conferences: Workshops and Conferences, 1992-2009 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Alianza de los Pueblos, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Committees: American Institute of Architects- Los Angeles River Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Committees: American Rivers, 1994-1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Committees: Bicycle Advisory Minutes, 1992-1997 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Committees: California Coastal Commission, 1998-2011 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Committees: City of Los Angeles River Task Force, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Committees: City of Los Angeles River Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Committees: City of Los Angeles River Task Force, 1992-1996 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Clean Water Network, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Committees: Community Events, 1991-2013 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Cornfield Park Advisory Committee, 2002 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Committees: Environmental Organizations, 1992-2011 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Committees: Environmental Water Leadership Council, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Erase the Waste, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Federal American Heritage Rivers Initiative, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Committees: Green Los Angeles Coalition, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Committees: Los Angeles City Ad Hoc River Committee, 2002-2006 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Los Angeles Conservation Corps, 1997-2008 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Committees: Los Angeles County Dept of Public Works (NPDES), 1993 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Committees: Los Angeles Integrated Resources Plan, 2002-2007 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Los Angeles River Appreciation Day, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Committees: Los Angeles River Outreach Sub-Taskforce, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Los Angeles River Revitalization Corp, 2011 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Meetings, 1993-2012 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Committees: National Park Service and Los Angeles River, 1997-2011 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Committees: Neighborhood Councils and Associations, 1992-2013 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Committees: Pacific American Volunteer Association, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Committees: Pacific Pipeline, 1991-1998 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Committees: Public Land Trust, 1992-2001 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Committees: Regional Water Quality Control Boards, 1990s-2000s (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Committees: Santa Monica Mountains Conservancy, 1990s-2000s (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Committees: State and Local Government Committee Meetings, 1990s-2000s (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Committees: Stormwater Task Force and Heal the Bay, 1993 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Tabling Information for Miscellaneous Events, 2000s (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Committees: Transit Projects, 1992-2011 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Committees: Unpave LA, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Education: Eco-Heroes, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Education: Los Angeles Unified School District, 2009-2011 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Education: Miscellaneous Education Programs, 2000s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Education: River Rover, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Education: River School, 2000s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Education: River School, 2000s (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
  - Education: River School Day, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Education: River School Student Artwork, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Education: Riverkeepers, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Events: Art Photos of Los Angeles River, 1930s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 21 October 2005 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 19 October 2007 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 4 October 2008 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta, 4 October 2010 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Events: Awards Dinner and Fiesta Photos, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Events: Awards Dinner Donor Prizes, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Events: Bridges on Los Angeles River, 1990-2012 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Events: Canoeing and kayaking Los Angeles River, 1990-2011 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Events: Canoeing and kayaking Los Angeles River, 1993-2011 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Events: Coastal Cleanup, 1992-2011 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Events: Down by the Los Angeles River Official Guide, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Events: Down by the Los Angeles River Walks, 1986-2011 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Events: Earth Day, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Events: Earth Day, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Events: Earth Day, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Events: Earth Day, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Events: Earth Day, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Events: Earth Day, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Events: Earth Day, Great Heron Gate, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Events: Earth Day, 2003-2012 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Events: Freeway in LA River Channel, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Events: Graffiti, 1990s-2000s (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Events: Huell Howser L.A. River Special, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Events: Los Angeles River Art Exhibitions, 1983-2002 (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
  - Events: Los Angeles River Artist Books, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Events: Los Angeles River and Film, 1986-2010 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Events: Los Angeles River and Poetry (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Events: Los Angeles River Fishing Survey, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Events: Los Angeles River Performance/Dance, 1990-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Events: Los Angeles River Reborn-Skirball Photo Exhibit, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Events: Los Angeles River Ride, 2000-2011 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Events: Los Angeles River Story Share, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Events: Man One/Mural Festival, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 7-9)
  - Events: Murals and Public Art, 1983-1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Events: Passport to the Los Angeles River, circa 1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Events: Photographic History of Los Angeles River Book, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Events: Plays, 1986-2011 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Events: Public Art Proposal, Helen Lessick, 2006-2007 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Events: Recreation Along L.A. River, 1995-2011 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Events: River Clean Up, 1990s-2000s (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Events: River Cleanup, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Events: River Katz (Leo Limon), 1991-2011 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Events: Sacred Path Project, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Events: Student Design Ideas, 1998-2008 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Events: T-Shirt Designs, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Events: Task Force Performance Art, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Events: Third Thursdays (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Events: Total Maximum Daily Load, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Events: Urban River Challenge, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - FoLAR Commendations, undated (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - FoLAR Event Photos, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Invitations and Correspondence, 1991-2001 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Member Letters and Acknowledgements, 2005-2011 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Lewis MacAdams' Statements and Writings, 1994-2007 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles River and Poetry, 2000 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, 2012 (Folder 158, Folder 3)
  - Projects: Biota of the Los Angeles River, 1989-2008 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Biota of the Los Angeles River Watershed, 2008 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Projects: Central Industrial Redevelopment Project, 2001-2004 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Projects: Cheonggyecheon River, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Projects: Chinatown Yard/Cornfield, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Projects: Chinatown Yard/Cornfield, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Projects: Chinatown Yard/Cornfield, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Projects: Chinatown Yard/Cornfield, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Chinatown Yard/Cornfield, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Projects: Chinatown Yard/Cornfield, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Projects: Chinatown Yard/Cornfield, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Projects: Chinatown Yard/Cornfield, 2007-2009 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Development Projects on Los Angeles River, 2001-2003 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Projects: El Pueblo Lake, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Projects: Freshwater Reservoir at Los Angeles River Mouth, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Projects: Gateway Park, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Projects: Isar River, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Projects: Isar River, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Joseph Beuys Fellowship, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Bikeway, 1990-2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Bikeway, 1990-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Bikeway, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Bikeway, 2000-2011 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Center, 1999-2011 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Greenway, 1987-1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Greenway, 2000s (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Lofts Development, 2006-2007 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Master Plan, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Master Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Master Plan, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Master Plan, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Master Plan, 2000-2004 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Master Plan, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Master Plan, 2007-2013 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Parks, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Parks, 2000s (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Performing Arts Center, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Recreation Survey, 2011 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Report Card, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Signage, 1992-2004 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Projects: Los Angeles River Watershed Monitoring Group, 2007 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Projects: River Clean Up Thank You to FoLAR, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Projects: Riverwatch, 1997-2007 (Box 29, Folder 1-6)
  - Projects: Riverwatch, 1997-2007 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Projects: Riverwatch, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Projects: Riverwatch, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Biological Monitoring, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Blank Forms (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Data, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Data, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 3-6)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Data, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Data, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 3-5)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Log Books, 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Log Books, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Material Safety Data, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Memos and Correspondence, 1997-2004 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Photo Logs, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Photos, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Procedures, 2002-2004 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Quality Monitoring Quality Assurance Plan, 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Sign Out Sheets, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Sites, 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Projects: Riverwatch Training, 2001-2004 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Projects: San Gabriel River Sampling, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Projects: Sister Rivers, 2008-2010 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Projects: State of the River, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Projects: Water Reclamation Project, 1988-1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Projects: Zanja Madre, 1998-2012 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Promotional T-shirts, 1998-2009 (Box 148, Box 149, Box 150)
  - Sites: Alameda Corridor Site, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Sites: Arroyo Seco Confluence with L.A. River, 1993-2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sites: Atwater Village Site, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Sites: Ballona Creek and Wetlands Site, 1996-2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sites: Boyle Heights, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Sites: Calabasas Creek Site, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sites: Compton Creek Site, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sites: Compton Creek Site, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Sites: Elysian Valley Site, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sites: Glendale Narrows Site, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sites: Griffith Park Site, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sites: Hazardous Waste Storage- Olympic Facility, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Sites: Headworks Spreading Grounds, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sites: Long Beach Site, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Sites: Long Beach Site, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Sites: Long Beach Site- City Associations, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sites: Long Beach Site- Dominguez Gap Restoration, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sites: Long Beach Site- Proposals, 2000s (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sites: Newhall Ranch Site, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sites: Piggyback Yard, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sites: Rio Hondo Site, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Sites: Sepulveda Basin Site, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sites: Studio City Site, 1990s-2000s (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Sites: Taylor Yard Site, 1992-2007 (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
  - Sites: Tujunga Wash, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Sites: Universal City Site, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Watershed Management, 1996-2000 (Box 147, Folder 6)